Bro, weather app said this
thing is going to be huge, man.
And so we're out here
on this tiny little boat?
This was your idea.
I know.
You know those weather reports
always exaggerate stuff anyway.
Hey, let's take a closer look.
Umm... maybe this is
a close enough look.
That storm looks like
it's moving pretty fast.
The water does
look kinda rough.
Maybe the weather
reports were right.
Is that...
Sharks.
And those waves
are coming towards us!
Uh, maybe we should head back.
-Yeah.
Nathan?
Yo, can this thing
go any faster?
It's the fastest
boat on the island!
Come on, hurry! This thing
is almost on top of us!
Hurry!
We gotta go, man,
that thing is getting close!
Come on!
It's as fast as it goes!
Great!
What happened?
Why are we slowing down?
The storm is right there, man!
Holy shit.
What? What is it?
The engine!
What do you mean, the engine?
We gotta go, man.
We gotta go!
Come on!
You gotta get back
in the boat, man.
You gotta get back in the boat!
Xavier! Xavier!
He fell in the water!
He's in the water somewhere!
Xavier!
Brace yourself!
Watch out!
All right, here we are, guys.
Sit in the car with him
for another hour?
Does it look a little
different from last year?
I don't think so.
Hey, you two,
start lugging.
Mark?
Hey, uh, Will, right?
Yeah, yeah,
good to see you again.
You too.
I couldn't stay away after
such a great vacation last year.
Hey, you remember
my family, right?
My wife, May,
and our son, Aeden?
Good to see you.
You remember my
beautiful wife, Sarah?
-Yeah, good to see you again.
-You ,too.
And Logan, Brooke.
-Hey guys.
-Hey.
Looking forward
to another barbecue.
Will still claims it's
the best burger he's ever had.
You have to tell
me how you do it.
Oh, yeah, I'm not ready to
give up that secret just yet.
It's so lovely, but
it's probably the only day
we're going to be
able to go to the beach.
There's supposed to be a
storm coming in the morning,
though, so we should probably
head to the beach today.
Oh man, I was really hoping
the weather would cooperate.
Well, the worst part of
the storm is projected
to go north, which
should be okay here.
At least that's what
the news is saying.
Still, it's better to enjoy a
sunny day at the beach, right?
Well, then we will definitely
make today a beach day,
right kids?
Well, hey, have fun.
We'll see you guys later.
We're off to grab
some fast food burgers
until you grill up
the real ones.
You better watch
this guy's cholesterol.
See ya.
-See you soon, guys.
-See you.
All right,
let the vacation begin.
Here we are.
Well, looks the same
as it did last year.
Yes, it does.
I don't know.
Smells kind of funny in here.
Logan, don't start.
Why don't we get settled
and we hit the beach?
The faster we get moving,
the faster I can work on my tan.
Okay.
Awww, is the beach
not your thing?
Oh no, Logan prefers to
be locked in his bedroom
24 hours a day
playing video games.
Video games won't
give me skin cancer.
They will destroy your eyesight.
Mm-hmm.
Teenagers.
Can we go into town?
Not yet. I want you to try to
enjoy the outside, Logan.
Lame.
So, where are you from again?
Right outside of Chicago.
Ah, I went there once.
My dad wanted to go
to a game at Wrigley.
I've never been.
Really?
Yeah, my parents
are White Sox fans.
I'm sorry.
It must be nice living
in a place like this
all year round.
It's all right.
You know, it gets
boring after a while, but...
Really?
I mean...
I could never get used to it.
The weather is so nice.
The weather is definitely fire.
Hey! You guys want
to head into town?
Sure.
So what's it like living
down here all year long?
Do you guys enjoy that?
Yeah, it's great.
I mean, you guys showed up
at kind of an unlucky time.
Oh my gosh.
Did you guys see
this about the storm?
It's... it's incredible.
I hope everyone's okay.
Yeah, you know,
the reports claimed
at least three
fatalities already.
Fortunately, that was
about 300 miles away.
I did hear the storm was
starting to slow
down a little bit.
Thank God.
Yeah, but the
weather these days?
It just keeps getting
worse and worse.
Thank climate change for that.
I know.
Wow, you're really good.
I've played this game
like a hundred times.
All that dedication is
definitely paying off.
So, have you ever
seen an ocean sunrise?
Not in Chicago.
You and I should
check it out tomorrow.
Yeah.
That would be great.
Um, but the storm, it looks
pretty bad, don't you think?
It'll miss us by
like 50 miles or so.
Might get a little wind.
Okay. What time?
Meet you at, like, 5 a.m.?
If you can get up that early.
I'll be up.
You guys?
We're leaving.
Um, gotta go.
See you there?
Definitely. 5 a.m.?
See you there.
I'll be in my room.
Would it be okay
if I woke up early
in the morning and went
and saw the sunrise?
Sunrise? You?
With who?
With Aeden.
Yeah, I suppose it'd be okay.
I don't think so, Mark.
You don't really know Aeden
that well.
We just hung out.
And you know his parents.
That doesn't mean you know him.
Your mom's right.
Step-mom.
Brooke, we can go together
one morning as a family.
-But I don't...
-No buts.
We're not going to
let you off alone
with some
boy you barely know.
You heard her.
She's never going to
respect me, is she?
You always let me
be the villain.
[door slams]
There it is.
Let's go.
[screams]
We were supposed to be
on a strict budget and
we already spent too
much money at the arcade.
I just wanted us
to have some fun.
It's vacation.
A vacation that we have
to drive the hatchback to
because we couldn't afford
payments on the SUV anymore.
Can we please just
not do this right now?
Can we just enjoy
ourselves while we're here?
I promise you I will deal
with things when we get home.
Sure.
Sorry I said anything.
Come on, hon.
Why don't you go to
bed if you're so tired?
Dad.
Oh boy, sorry,
it's the sun.
Really takes it right
out of you, huh?
Okay.
You coming?
You're going to bed?
I suppose so.
All right.
-We're not finished playing.
-Good night.
Play solitaire.
Night.
I'm going to go to bed, too.
What?
Why?
Got early morning plans?
No. I guess I'm just
tired from sun, too.
Fine.
I'm on vacation.
And I think I deserve
to have a little bit of fun.
Yeah.
I mean, if I don't
tell Mom and Dad,
what are you going to do for me?
I'll...
I'll buy you that stupid
video game you want. Okay?
-The deluxe version?
-Yeah. Sure. The deluxe version.
Whatever that means.
But wait, what if Mom and Dad
get up before you get back?
Then you better come
up with a good cover.
You get me the video game,
I'll give you an alibi.
Deal?
Deal.
[spits]
-Hey.
-Parents cool with you going?
-Yeah. Totally.
Awesome.
Shall we?
I love the smell of the ocean.
Yeah, it's right over that
hill. Check it out in a minute.
-Yo.
-Yo, Isaac.
This is Brooke.
Brooke, Isaac.
-Hey.
While you guys
have some fun,
I'm going to get some fishin'
in before the rain starts.
Yeah, we're just going
to go check out sun rise.
Try to.
Be my guest.
I'll go back to the truck
and get more beers.
Beers?
Maybe grab some cola, too.
-You got it.
-Okay.
I'm really glad you came.
Yeah, me too.
I definitely needed it.
Want to get away from
your parents, huh?
That and my brother.
I can definitely
understand that.
I'm surprised they
even let you come out.
Yeah, about that.
They didn't know you're here.
I thought I was
the bad influence.
I'm not a bad influence.
I just...
There's some weird stuff going
on with my dad and step-mom.
I just need to get away.
Something's going on?
My dad lost his job as a nurse.
-Sorry.
-It's fine. He got a new one.
He's a paramedic.
But it doesn't
exactly pay the same.
At all.
So...
All they do is talk about money
all the time.
Like, all the time.
It's just things are...
Well... I'm glad
I could be a distraction.
At least a little bit.
Me too.
Nice view.
Yeah.
Maybe we'll catch the
sunrise another day.
Do you always bring
out-of-towners up here?
No.
Just you.
[thunder]
Whoa!
That was really loud.
Should we go?
Yo, Isaac.
What's up?
The storm's path is changing.
A surge is coming.
We should get off the beach.
I thought you said
it wouldn't get this bad.
Sometimes weather
has a mind of its own.
We should get out of here.
And go where?
Into town.
Come on.
It's really raining.
The storm.
I guess it didn't
miss us like they said.
We should find cover.
We can wait it out 'til
the rain lets up.
No, what about the surge
that Isaac mentioned?
It'll be fine.
You don't want to be
on the beach in a surge.
What's going on?
I don't know.
Oh my God, I thought
the worst of the storm
was supposed to pass us.
I don't know.
These storms have been known
to turn on a dime
more and more often these days.
Where's Brooke?
Brooke?
Brooke!
She's gone.
What?
Logan...
Where's your sister?
Logan.
Come on.
How dangerous would
the beach be right now?
Please do not tell me that
she snuck out this morning.
Well, I'm sorry,
she wanted to go.
She told me she'd buy me a
video game if I didn't
say anything.
A video game?
She's at the beach.
Damn it, Logan!
Why didn't you tell us
the moment she left?
I was asleep when she left!
She just told me last night!
Well, then you should
have told us last night.
Correct.
Call her.
This is Brooke,
please leave a message.
Brooke, Brooke, honey,
please call us back
and let us
know where you are.
We're not mad.
We're just worried.
-Straight to voicemail.
-Great.
[knocking]
Is Aeden here?
We told him last night
he couldn't go because
of the weather.
We told Brooke that
she couldn't go either.
We need to find them.
What? Out there?
Yeah, before it gets worse.
The first part of the storm
usually isn't the most severe.
-No!
-Logan, not now.
Why?
Because your sister
is out there, that's why.
Well, her and Aeden are probably
in a building or something.
Well, you don't know that.
Listen to me. Storm or not,
we are going out there
to find them.
If the storm is severe enough
to have caused a surge,
we need to find Aeden and Brooke
before the next surge hits.
That's when flooding
will be at its worst.
How bad are we talking, here?
This town is in a basin,
and tends to fill with
water in a storm.
Highest on record was six feet,
but that was before my time.
Either way, the beach isn't
safe at all right now.
Even if the storm bypasses us,
the surges are way too severe.
Okay.
Babe, you stay here with Logan
in case Brooke and Aeden come.
-But Dad!
-Logan, no buts!
You should have told us.
Let's go.
We'll be back.
We'll be right back.
Will it ever stop raining?
Aeden?
We need... we need
to move further inland.
Has it ever been
this high up before?
It'll stop soon.
It's so cold.
At least it's morning.
So the lights being out
won't be as big a deal.
The surge has already
taken over the whole town.
So we can't outrun it.
There's no telling what
kind of debris
could already
be in the water.
There!
The ladder?
It only takes
like six inches of water
to sweep someone off their feet.
And with how fast it's moving...
No, can't we just like hide
in a store or something?
They're all still closed.
And the water's
rising too quick.
We need to get above it.
Coral Bay sits in a basin,
so it floods easy.
The first floor of these places
will be flooded in no time.
We'll be fine.
We need to keep climbing
and wait for the rain to recede.
Come on.
You go first.
You're doing great.
Gah!
Aeden, are you okay?
I'm fine! Go!
And a tropical storm warning
is in effect until 8pm.
Authorities are urging
people to find shelter
and stay off the streets as
the worst part of the storm,
as well as a second surge
with potentially even more
catastrophic flooding
won't hit for a few more hours.
That's not good.
I cannot believe
they went out in this.
Brooke usually doesn't
do things like this.
I don't know, maybe
she's acting out because,
honestly, things haven't
been going so great at home.
Especially...
Aeden is usually
more responsible.
Where on the beach
did you say they are?
Uh...
Up here, take a left!
You can't be serious when
you say that this is normal.
No. It's not.
So what do we do?
I don't know.
I really hope
my family's okay.
My family will help them.
They'll know what to do.
Our houses are
further from the beach,
so the water won't
be as high there,
if it even manages
to get over the seawall.
There's something out there.
That's my friend!
Isaac! Isaac!
Isaac, hey!
Hey! Hey, Isaac!
-Isaac, up here! Isaac!
-Isaac!
Isaac, get to the ladder!
Aeden!
-Isaac, get up here!
-Isaac!
Isaac, come here!
Come on, get to the ladder!
Isaac, come on! Hurry!
I'm coming!
Isaac, hurry!
Isaac, hurry up!
Ah!
[screams]
Isaac!
No! No! No!
No...
You know, I really
think we should start
preparing in case
we have to evacuate.
Evacuate?
Yeah, let's get some bottles
of water together,
some non-perishables,
and oh, if you have
a first aid kit.
You know, if the news
had said that it was
going to be this awful,
I could have prepared better.
I have a ton of
sandbags in the garage.
I mean, storms
have come through here.
Bad storms,
but this is just...
Insane.
Yeah... yeah.
What is that?
Is that water?
Did you see him?
-Did you think it was a--
-No!
No way!
We didn't see any blood.
He's probably just got
carried away with the current.
He's a good swimmer.
He'll be fine.
We need to get off this roof.
And go where?
Because I'm not getting
back in that water.
I don't know.
Not with what just
happened to Isaac!
I don't know, okay?
We can't stay here.
It's not safe.
We could get stuck by lightning.
How much further?
About two blocks.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
I mean, the beach was here.
Could never imagine
a storm surge this deep.
I can't believe the surge
can get worse than this.
I hope the kids find
someplace safe.
Brooke!
Aeden!
-Brooke!
-Aeden!
Do you hear that?
-Brooke!
-Aeden!
-Dad?
-Dad! Dad, we're up here!
-Dad!
Up here! Dad!
Dad, come on!
Brooke!
-Brooke!
-Where are they?
Brooke!
-Aeden!
-Dad!
There!
Dad, up here!
Dad!
Thank you, thank you.
We're coming, Aeden!
Brooke, Brooke,
stay there, baby!
Come on.
-No, Dad!
-Dad! Shark!
Get out of the water!
Dad, there's sharks!
Sharks in the water!
Brooke, stay there, baby!
We're coming!
Dad, get out of the water!
Dad, there's sharks
in the water!
Watch out, sharks!
-What did she say?
-What's she saying?
I can't hear what
they're saying!
-Sharks in the water!
-I don't know.
-Dad, come on!
-Sharks in the water!
Dad!
Get out of the water! Dad!
What's he say?
Sharks?
What?
Don't move.
Move, come on!
Dad, be careful!
-Get out of the water!
-Dad, come on!
Get out of the water!
There's sharks!
Jesus, what do we do?
We need to get out of the water.
But where?
There!
Not too fast, but move!
We do't want to draw attention!
Come on!
Dad, look out!
Dad, help!
Dad, don't go,
there's sharks!
Okay.
Move slowly.
Slow movements, Will.
-Dad, come on!
-Be careful!
[grunts]
Will, come on, man!
Keep going!
You're almost there!
Okay.
I got you, bro, swim!
Swim!
No, no, move!
Come on, I got you!
I got you, Will! Come on!
Give me your hand!
Dad! Hurry!
Dad! Dad, come on!
Give me... give me your hand!
Give me your hand,
I'll pull you up!
Hurry! Hurry, come on!
-Dad!
-Dad! Dad, help him!
Dad!
Give me your hand!
No!
No, Dad! No!
-Dad!
-Dad! Help him!
No!
Dad!
Dad, no! No!
It's still just a busy signal
and nobody's answering 911.
It's not stopping.
It's almost to the windows.
Have you ever seen
a surge this high?
No, no. Like I said earlier,
I mean,
we've had some bad storms, but
this is completely different.
I don't know why
this is happening.
Oh God, I hope that Will
and Mark have the kids.
Of course he does.
If I know my husband,
and I do, he's made it his
mission to find them
-and take them to safety, okay?
-Okay.
They're probably on
a boat somewhere.
Everything will be fine.
Mom?
What?
What is it?
Can sharks come
this far onto land?
I've never seen it.
I mean...
I mean, if that's sea water,
then I'm sure they can.
All right,
I have to do something.
Hey, up here!
Use the ladder!
Hurry, while the sharks
are distracted!
Dad, be careful!
Sir, let me help you.
Hey, you all right, man?
Don't worry man,
we got ya.
Thank you.
Brooke!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm fine.
How's Aeden?
I don't know.
Just hold on tight, baby!
Is that your kid?
It's my daughter, Brooke!
I'm Ray.
Tasha!
I went to school
with Aeden's parents.
Bill was a good guy.
Huh, poor kid.
I'm Mark.
Thank you both
for saving my life.
Hey, man, don't mention it.
Ray here's a local fisherman.
One of the best.
And you?
I'm Tasha, like I said. I'm a
bartender down the street.
I was on my way
home when all this hit.
If it wasn't for Ray,
I'd be chum in the water.
Hey, man, it was nothing.
Hey! Despite this being a
place that has frequent storms,
a lot of these
buildings are wood
because it's cheaper
and easier to replace
in case they get
damaged or destroyed.
What are you getting at, Ray?
What I'm getting at is
those kids, the building
they're on, it's the least
stable building in Coral Bay.
The owner is one cheap bastard.
If that water keeps rising,
there's no guarantee
that it's gonna hold.
Are you telling me that
that building could collapse?
With the lumber
he used to make it?
Yeah.
What about this building?
Is it good?
It's better.
Okay, so we need to figure out
how to get them
over here with us.
Look, even if we
can get them over here,
we gotta get
to dry land eventually.
As long as we're in the water,
surrounded by water,
we're screwed.
This water ain't gonna recede
until after high tide
tonight around 7:00.
And there ain't gonna be any
rescue coming
until that water stops rising.
That last radar image I saw,
the worst of it is still
gonna come down.
The radio said
the same thing,
with the warning not
ending till later tonight.
The problem is, Coral Bay is
basically this
15 square mile basin.
Now if this part's
already covered in water
this close to shore,
we're gonna have to
go several miles
through water
just to get to town.
Now wait, there's
a couple of places
in town that's got
a higher elevation.
Just one battle at a time, okay?
Right now I need to
figure out how to get
Brooke and Aeden over here
with us on this building
before we figure out
how to get to higher ground.
Yeah, agreed.
Wait, you think that ladder
that you used to get me up,
would that reach
across that building to them?
Yeah, I think it might,
but just barely.
Okay.
Then we gotta get it over there
and just hold it
real tight, okay?
Let's do it.
Brooke!
Hey, baby,
we need to get you guys
off that building and
over here with us!
Dad! Dad!
It's making noises!
It's not stable!
It could collapse!
I'm not getting
back into that water!
You won't go in that
water, baby, I promise you!
We're going to lay
the ladder down
for you guys to crawl across!
Will that work?
Just go one at a time, okay?
I'm gonna hold it tight!
Just need to be
real careful, you got it?
Okay, I got it.
We're gonna cross over and
we're gonna meet my dad, okay?
What's the point?
What?
You saw what
those sharks did!
Yeah, well, we can't stay here!
The water's rising and
the who knows how much longer!
Look, I know you're hurting!
You gotta do it, okay?
Just do it for me!
And just do it for your
mom, okay?
Okay!
Let's do this!
Let's get it!
Here we go!
Easy now.
We're coming, baby!
-Steady!
-It's not gonna reach!
It'll reach!
-Hold on.
-Hold tight.
-Come on.
-Here I go.
Okay, Brooke.
Be careful.
-Take it slow.
-Okay.
Don't worry, hon.
You got this.
Come on, now.
Easy.
Careful! Don't look down!
-Keep going!
-Keep going, nice.
Ah!
-Careful, kid!
-You got this!
You got this, girl.
You can do it.
You got this, baby.
[screams]
Ah!
We got you, Brooke!
We got you!
Come on, you're almost there!
Let's go!
I'm okay!
I got it!
You got this, Brooke.
[grunts]
You okay?
Aeden, it's your turn,
you're next! You got this!
We got you, don't worry!
-Come on, Aeden!
-Easy.
Aeden, now it's your turn.
Don't look down, okay?
-Keep it steady.
-Keep going!
You're doing great!
-You can do it.
-Just don't look down.
Don't think about it,
just go.
Okay.
-Come on, man, you got this.
-Come on, Aeden!
Don't look down!
-That's it.
-Stay focused, buddy!
You got it, Aeden!
Don't look down!
-Come on, Aeden.
-You're almost there.
You got this.
Great job, Aeden.
It's all right.
You're okay.
Yeah, come on.
Great job, Aeden.
Keep moving.
Ah!
Come on, Aeden.
You can do it!
You okay?
Come on! Come on, Aeden!
You got this!
Let's go, buddy!
There you go.
Great job.
We still have a couple of
rafts on this side of the house,
so if we can make it over
there, we can just use those.
What if we can't?
Well, then we're
gonna find another way.
Here, take this.
Come on!
[thudding]
What was that?
-Oh my God!
[shouting]
-Go!
-Logan, come on!
[screaming]
Mae!
No, Mom, no!
No! Mom!
Oh my God.
Son...
Hey, hey.
Hey, it's okay.
Baby, look at me.
Will you just stay calm?
That door's not gonna
hold up much longer.
We need to get out of here.
She had rafts on the porch.
Okay.
Come on, come.
Come on!
We got it!
[shouting]
Here, take this.
Take this.
Oh my God!
Have you ever rowed
a canoe before?
We just need to survive
the next surge till tonight!
Tonight?
Hey, where you guys from?
You local?
No, we came here on vacation.
My wife and my son are
still back at the rental home.
Where?
Seashell Lane.
They were staying
right next to...
Sorry about your dad, Aeden.
I really am. He's a good guy.
Dad, I'm so sorry.
Hey, no, no.
Don't you worry about it, okay?
We just gotta find a way back
to your mom and your brother.
Dad?
We need to find a
way off of this building.
This is only the first surge.
The second surge is
gonna get even worse.
One more hit like that, and
we're gonna end up
back in the drink.
Where are we gonna go?
We can't just...
There are sharks.
Hey, I got a boat
over in the marina
just a couple
of blocks away.
Now if we can get
over there, maybe
we can ride out
the storm in it.
Maybe even sail away.
She's a powerful old girl.
She's seen plenty of weather.
We're gonna need
a bigger boat.
We better figure this
out quick because this
building isn't standing
for much longer.
I agree.
These buildings aren't safe.
We're gonna end up
getting trapped in town.
We need to get
across that water fast.
We can't jump off into the water
from here because
of all the debris.
We need to find a
way down a floor or two
and climb out a window
into the water.
Then we can maybe
use the debris
as rafts to get
to the marina.
Does that sound good?
Yeah, sounds like a plan.
But if it isn't the sharks,
gotta watch out
for downed power lines.
That electricity goes
through saltwater
faster than fresh water.
Thanks for the fun fact, Ray.
Any time.
Let's go.
There's a door over there.
Easy.
-I can't see.
-Just follow me.
-You okay?
-Yeah. Never better, Ray.
We need to hurry or this place
is gonna collapse on top of us!
Okay. This will do.
I'll go out first and
I'll stop some debris.
Then we can use that
to float to the harbor.
Careful.
Okay, come on.
Hurry, Aeden.
Brooke.
Okay, Aeden. You all right?
You're doing okay.
All right, we got this.
Aeden, come on.
Let's go.
Aeden, grab onto this.
Come on!
It's coming down.
Ray.
Come on, Ray.
The building's coming down.
-Hurry up!
-Come on, Ray! Hurry!
Come on!
Ray!
Let's go.
We gotta go.
Get out here.
We gotta paddle, let's go.
Mom! Mom!
Where's Brooke?
We're gonna find her and
your father. Don't worry.
Come on.
[shouts]
Keep going.
You got this.
Hey, Mom.
There's a cop!
Maybe Brooke will be with them!
Yeah, maybe.
Come on!
Mom!
Mom, the water! The water!
Babe, come on!
Hang on!
[shouts]
Mom!
We have to get out of the water!
Over here!
Go! There!
Come on, come on!
Give me your hand!
Watch it! Watch it!
Move!
Move, move, move!
Give me your hand!
Are you all right?
-I think so.
-I'll tell you what.
The goddamn water's infested
with those damn things.
I'll tell you what.
Blood, and all that debris.
That's attracting 'em.
Right now, outside, there's
nothing more than just a...
a big... death pit.
I'm telling you.
[screams]
Yeah.
Keep an eye out for sharks.
Don't worry about it.
Just keep moving.
Easier said than done, Ray.
Can't count the number
of them bastards
I've caught
over the years.
Kind of unnerving.
We're almost there.
Ray?
Where's the marina?
The storm submerged
all the boats.
This storm, it got bigger
than it was supposed to be.
Bigger than anything
that's hit this town.
And it ain't done yet.
Is there another boat
that we can grab?
No. All the boats
were in the marina.
There's nothing left.
-Aeden!
Aeden!
I got you.
Aeden, Aeden.
It's okay. You're okay.
Brooke, you good?
-Okay?
-I got him. Calm down.
Okay, you're good.
Look!
Hey! Get in that raft
before the sharks get us!
Keep swimming!
You got it, honey.
-Come on.
-Come on!
-Okay. Give me your hand.
-Let's go. Come on.
Come on!
You got it.
Aeden, you're next.
Let's go.
Got room for one more?
Okay.
-Ray!
Are you gonna get in?
I am not getting in that boat.
What do we do now?
I used up my one idea.
And it was a pretty bad one.
-Natasha?
-Okay.
So, we can try Silky's.
It's the boat that I work at.
It's not too far from here.
And it's on higher ground.
Faith, the owner says
that it can survive
Biblical flooding
because it's built so
close to the beach and I could
really go for a shot right now.
Oh yeah.
Tasha's right. If it survives,
that's going to be
the best place to be for
when the Coast Guard comes.
And we've got to
get some shelter.
The worst of the storms
will be hitting
along with that second surge.
I think Silky's is probably
the sturdiest building
around other than the
Manis Beach Lighthouse.
That lighthouse is too far away.
It's a long shot.
If I had to put
money on anything
that's still standing,
it'd be Silky's.
Okay, but I'm not going anywhere
without rescuing
my wife or my son.
We're not going anywhere
without Mom and Logan!
No, we can't let them down.
Hey, you've got
to save yourself
before you can save anyone else.
Okay, we're going
to regroup at Silky's
and we will come
up with a new plan.
-All right?
-Okay, don't worry.
First round of drinks on me.
Paddle, paddle.
Come on.
Dennis, you knucklehead.
He knew to be more careful.
He was a...
He was not a rookie.
My name's Faith.
This is my establishment.
Locals.
Stephen...
Mary...
Noah.
I'm Sarah.
This is Logan.
Silky's has stood
straight since 1966.
And no salt water has
ever gotten on my floor.
You're safe here.
No, we're not!
Listen, a shark got
in our house.
This town is a fishbowl.
The reason that we have survived
is we are above
the flood level, okay?
He's seen someone he knows
get killed today.
I thinks it's safe to say that
we've all lost someone tonight.
I don't even know where
his sister or my husband are.
And... Mae did not deserve...
Mae?
Mae Baldwin?
Is she...
Yeah.
I'm really sorry to hear that.
She's, um...
She was a good person.
So how do we plan on
getting out of all of this?
We sit and wait.
For the water to go away
and the cavalry to show up.
Anything else is just too risky.
Those sharks.
Faith?
This building isn't
gonna fall apart, is it?
There's no guarantee
on anything,
but I think she'll hold.
Been through a lot.
She's still standing.
Hey.
You have seen things today that
nobody should have to see, okay?
And I'm really sorry about that.
But I'm going to...
Look at me. Look at me.
I'm going to make sure that
we get out of here, okay?
Okay, come here.
It's okay.
I love you.
Woo! Look!
It's still standing!
Thank God.
I want to thank you for
keeping Brooke safe tonight.
We kept each other safe.
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have
been at the beach this morning.
It's okay.
Okay, baby?
Paddle, everybody!
This boat is taking
on a lot of water.
I don't know if it's gonna
stay afloat until we get there.
Oh, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no!
We're caught!
Let's go! Paddle!
Paddle faster!
Come on! Come on!
Boilermakers.
This was Denni' favorite drink.
He did not care what kind of
whiskey I gave him,
what kind of beer.
This was his drink.
I remember one night,
a bunch of college kids came in,
hooting and hollering.
But... Dennis hated it
when the younger crowd hated it.
Bartenders loved it,
because that's the only time
they could actually
make some money.
Not like the 50-cent tips
Dennis would give them.
The college kids
started doing shots.
So Dennis challenged them to see
who could do the
most Boilermakers.
They had no idea
what it even was.
But they were game.
So he let them choose
the whiskey,
let them choose the beer.
I was serious when
I said he did not care.
I watched them do
one, two, three, four down.
Nobody even seemed fazed.
He really got those
college kids, huh?
No.
They drank him under the table.
Dennis fell asleep with
his head on the bar
until after the close.
I am going to miss
that knucklehead.
Coral Bay is not going
to be the same after this.
-To Dennis.
-Dennis!
Go! Climb the ladder!
Let's go! Go! Come on!
Brooke!
Okay, got you!
Come on.
Go, Aeden.
Come on. You got this.
You can do it, buddy.
That's it.
Okay.
Good job.
There's a door over there!
I got you!
Come on, Ray.
Silky's still standing!
-Sarah? Sarah, we're here!
-Faith! Faith!
-Brooke!
-Mom!
Oh my God! Logan!
Hey, it's okay.
It's okay, it's okay.
How bad is it?
This is the worst
I've ever seen
and it's only
getting uglier.
It's not letting up.
What's the town?
It's, uh, it's underwater.
It's crazy.
Good God.
Oh, God.
I'm so sorry.
Where's my mother?
Is she here?
Did she come with you guys?
Is she still at home?
What?
What is it?
Honey...
Why are you crying?
-I'm so sorry.
-No... No.
No!
I'm so sorry.
No... No...
He lost both of
his parents tonight.
Aeden, if you need anything,
we're all here for you, okay?
Ray.
I want to introduce
you to my family.
This is...
This is my wife, Sarah.
And my son, Logan.
They saved us out there tonight.
Thank you so much.
Just pay the favor forward.
I'll be forever grateful for
you.
Hey, you guys.
All Silky's has to do
is get us through this
second surge and the
strongest part of the storm,
and we're going to
be over this nightmare.
[screams]
Faith, no!
Go, go, go!
Go to the roof!
Go to the roof! Go!
Tasha! Come on!
Let's go!
Move, move!
No! No! I won't!
He saved me!
He's all I got left!
Then I can't leave him, either.
Come on, your family needs you.
Go! Go!
Go! Both of you!
Come on, you son of a bitch.
No!
Ray!
Is everyone here?
Is everyone okay?
Yeah, the kids are here.
You feeling okay?
Tasha? Where's Ray?
He's gone!
Are we safe up here?
No.
Nowhere is safe.
No! Nowhere is safe!
Okay, this building is not
going to stand for much longer.
And if the storm is too
much for Silky's...
Then we need to
figure something out.
And if that completely
breaks loose...
There!
We need to get there.
Right!
That is a bit of a swim in
shark-infested waters, guys.
Well, one way or another,
we're going to end up
back in that water.
And tha's the only place I see.
Unlike all these buildings,
it shouldn't fall apart.
Okay. There.
There's no live wires.
The water is so cold,
we have to try to find
a way to stay out of it
for as long as we can
or we're going
to all risk getting hypothermia
on top of everything else.
Another thing to
add to the list, right?
Look, in just a little bit,
we can drive right
out of this basin,
away from these sharks,
and get out of this water, okay?
Okay? We've just got to
find a way to get to it.
Maybe more debris?
Sounds like we got to go now.
All right! Right now
before we get electrocuted!
Okay, I'm gonna go first
and help everyone else down.
Let's go!
Go! Go! Hurry up!
Okay, we have no choice.
We've just got to
jump and swim for it!
Okay! I'm going in!
Come on!
Brooke, Aeden, let's go!
Aeden! Are you okay?
My leg.
It's cramping again.
You guys ready?
No!
Come on!
Oh, God.
Mom, come on.
[shrieks]
-Logan!
I got you!
You okay?
-No! No!
-Keep moving!
Get moving!
Keep swimming.
I got you, come on.
You got this.
I see it.
-That big truck!
-I see it! Come on!
We'll get to it.
Keep swimming!
Come on!
I got you.
Come on.
-Tasha, Tasha!
-Come on!
Come on.
Come on, baby.
You got this.
Come on, girl.
Take her!
You got this?
Hold on!
Mark! Mark! There's a shark!
There's sharks!
Come on!
Mark, you gotta
get out of the water!
Got it?
-All right, everybody inside!
-All right.
Okay, it's empty.
Come on!
Get in the back!
Let's get this thing started.
We can drive to higher ground.
-I got it.
-You got the keys?
All right.
[engine sputters]
Damn it!
Try again.
Come on, come on.
Damn it!
Okay.
Okay, don't worry, okay?
Because this thing's
on top of the hill,
we should be able to
ride out the second surge.
We'll ride it out in here.
Together.
As a family.
Okay, all right.
Let's go.
We're safer back here.
Come on.
Aeden, are you okay?
Not really.
Hey.
Promise me you'll
hold it together,
and I promise you that
I will get us out of here.
Okay?
I know that you've
had a hell of a night,
and that truck wouldn't start,
but someone will
eventually come for us.
Okay?
In the meantime,
why don't we try to
look out for another
vehicle or any other
buildings that, uh,
that won't be compromised,
just in case...
Mark...
Mark, no.
There is nothing else.
If Silky's couldn't
stand the storm,
then there are no
buildings standing.
The thing was
built like a bunker.
No, what about the
lighthouse that Ray mentioned?
It's ancient, okay?
Even if it survived
the first surge,
it's not going to survive
the second time.
I'm sorry about all this.
I'm sorry about the stress
that I caused by losing my job.
I'm sorry that I thought
a vacation would help us.
No, it feels so silly now.
It all feels so silly now.
I'm just...
I'm just glad that
we're all together.
And we're all still alive.
I love you.
Why doesn't anyone
come to rescue us?
It's not safe.
Not until that
second surge is over.
Isn't it like people's jobs
or something
to go into
dangerous places?
Buddy, as a paramedic, our core
principle is scene safety.
Which means you can't
rescue anyone
if you're killed
or injured first.
As long as that second surge
doesn't hit us, we'll be okay.
We just have to
hold on a couple more hours
until the water recedes and
then someone will come for us.
More hours?
Um...
Was my mom mad at
me when you last saw her?
No, honey.
Honey, listen to me.
She was not mad.
She was just worried.
I just... I just don't want
her last thoughts
to have been, like,
angry ones.
I just want to go home.
We will go home
eventually, buddy, okay?
I promise you.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Okay, okay.
Well, we gotta go now
because it's flooding, guys.
Come on, let's go!
Dad!
No, no, okay.
It's gonna be okay.
You know what?
When the water recedes,
the boats and helicopters,
they'll be able to see
us better from up here.
We're gonna go.
We're gonna be okay.
All right, kids first!
Let's go!
Let's go! Hurry!
-We're gonna be okay.
-Let's go!
Come on.
Come on, one at a time.
Hurry!
I'm trying!
-Aeden!
-Ow!
Aeden!
Brooke!
What happened?
-Brooke!
Aeden!
Mark, the kids are in the water!
I got it!
Hang on!
Come on!
I gotta get Brooke. Go!
Mark, hurry!
Come on, honey!
I'm stuck!
What? Where is she?
She's stuck!
I can't get her up!
Come on, try to
get out of there!
It's not a shark, is it?
Where are they?
Mark, I'm coming to help!
No, Tasha!
Come on, you gotta move!
There's at least three
coming right at you!
Mark!
Come on! Come on!
Give me your hand!
-Swim!
-I'm trying!
Swim, Brooke!
Mark! Mark!
You got her?
You good?
I got you!
Mark, come back!
Come on, Mark,
get back in here!
Come on, let her go!
There are three sharks
coming right at you!
-Faster!
-Come on, hurry up!
-Tasha!
-No!
-I gotta go get her!
-No, no, no!
I gotta go get her!
-Honey, stop!
-Tasha!
No! It's too late!
I'm so sorry!
I think we're moving!
I think we're floating!
The second surge is hitting!
Hang on!
It's on fire!
The transformer blew!
We have to get off of
here before we get hit!
We have to jump, guys!
We have no choice!
Ready?
On the count of three!
One! Two! Three!
Are you guys good?
Everyone okay?
Try to keep moving!
Conserve your energy!
Brooke! Brooke!
Hey, hey, hey!
You need to breathe, okay?
You need to stay conscious.
You're going into shock.
Okay, listen to me.
Listen to me.
When it's high tide...
-No!
Things will hopefully
get better, okay?
Just keep moving.
Help will eventually come.
Do you hear that?
I think it's a helicopter!
What are you
talking about, Logan?
Did you see that?
It was right there!
-Lightning!
-It's okay.
It's hypothermia.
You need to relax.
Where'd it go?
It's okay.
It's okay, buddy.
Hey! We need to get our
body temperatures up.
Keep moving!
Come on.
What is that?
I see something, too!
Keep moving.
We got this. We got this.
It's a lighthouse.
Manis Beach lighthouse.
We must have traveled
several miles from downtown.
It's still standing!
Okay, we just need
to make it there.
If we get inside, we can
ride the rest of this out.
She's withstood
the storm's so far.
Can we make it?
We've come this far.
Come on!
We need to hurry
before we have to
fight against the tide.
Go!
To the lighthouse!
Keep moving!
Sharks are coming!
I'm going.
I can't make it.
Sharks! Sharks!
Keep going!
[gasps]
No!
[gasping, coughing]
-Logan...
-What's that?
-Come on!
-Help me out!
-Mom, Mom, Mom, Mom!
-Hold her head.
Oh my God.
I'm gonna start compressing.
Straighten her feet.
Mom!
-Stay with me, Sarah.
-Mom?
-Come on, baby. Come on.
-Please, open your eyes, Mom.
Stay with me, Sarah.
Sarah? Sarah?
Oh, baby! Baby!
[helicopter approaching]
Look!
Over here! Please!